thepaktv.com 2014-09-29

# ThePakTv: Watch Pakistani Dramas & Political Shows in High Quality - Privacy Policy of ThePakTv.com

_Privacy Policy:_

GeoPakTv.com care about how your personal information is used and shared, and we take your privacy seriously. Please read the following terms to learn more about our privacy policy. 

By [registering](http://www.thepaktv.net/forums/register.php) to GeoPakTv.com you are accepting the practices outlined in this Privacy Policy. 

We will never sell your personal information, or use it for any other purpose other than logging in/out, demographics for our knowledge, and any voluntary feature of the site. 

We use cookies with minimal information in them. 

We use Google Analytics, which is covered by Google’s Privacy policy 

We allow you to contact other members via profile pages, but no private information is sent unless you want them to see. 

If you are below 13 then you can NOT use this forum. Do NOT register if you are below the age of 13.

In details What does GeoPakTv.com Privacy Policy Covers? All the personal information we collect is noted on your profile page. That includes your name, email, date of birth and biographic information. The personal information that you provide is used for Registration purpose. In order for you to participate in GeoPakTv.com discussion you must complete a registration form. As part of registration form, we require your email address. 

_Profile Information_

GeoPakTv.com allow other users to browse your full name, instant messaging URL, and other details within your member profile should you provide this optional information. GeoPakTv.com allows for the RSS syndication of all of its public content within the website.
